ANDRIY NOSOV



Ternopil, Ukraine | REMOTE





FRONTEND DEVELOPER





+38(067) 909 86 40



nosovandriy@gmail.com

HARD SKILLS

- FUNDAMENTALS: Javascript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS
- JS FRAMEWORKS: React. NextJS
- CSS FRAMEWORKS: SCSS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, MUI
- BUILD TOOLS: NPM, Babel, Redux, Vercel
- TOOLS: Git, Github, VSCode, Chrome Dev
- OTHERS: Figma, Jira, SEO, UX/UI
- ENGLISH: Intermediate (B1)

SOFT SKILLS

- ACCOUNTABILITY
- SELF-LEARNING
- PATIENCE
- CRITICAL THINKING
- COMMUNICATION SKILLS

EDUCATION

- Ternopil Ivan Puluj National **Technical University** Master's degree Computer Engineering
- Mate Academy Front End development

ABOUT ME

As a Junior Frontend Developer, I have experience with a stack of technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Rest API and others.

I'm a graduate of Ternopil National Technical University, majoring in computer engineering. I have an intermediate level of English, good communication skills, which I have acquired from previous workplaces, and the responsibility for working in a team. I also have good self-learning skills, which helps me acquire new knowledge.

EXPERIENCE

2022-2023 - COMMERCIAL PROJECTS

In my last project, I created a website store on NexsJS. This framework has integrated Image Optimization, handy Routing, and SSR which improves performance and SEO. Also, I applied Tailwind, Redax toolkit, and Axios. I implemented the ability to receive order data in the Telegram bot and integrated the Google Analytics service.

• CheeseCake shop nahirna-cake.com.ua

(7)

• Logistic company ukrainets.in.ua

(7)

2021-2022 - PET PROJECTS

• Todo App (React, HTML, CSS, SCSS, REST API)

• Route Table (React, HTML, React Router, REST API) 🔘 🔀



• Employees Table (JS, HTML, CSS, SCSS)

Dia website (HTML, CSS, SCSS)

Bakery website (HTML, CSS, SCSS)

OTHER PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SE CHORTKIVSKYI KHP

• 2013-2020 - Head of Sales Department

My job responsibilities involved trading grains and wheat flour in Ukraine. In addition, I implemented the export functionality abroad, which allowed exporting products to countries such as Azerbaijan, China. Moldova. and EU countries.

TETRA CONSULTING

- 2010-2012 Hardware Sales Manager My job consisted of working with product vendors, buying and selling computer hardware and other related equipment.
- 2008–2010 Computer Repair Technician I was responsible for diagnosing and repairing computer hardware. In addition, I was involved in assembling custom PCs.